Guide to the Anthony Barboza papers, ca. 1970-1999.
Barboza, Anthony papers
- Photographs
  - Actors, Artists and Celebrities
    - Amiri Baraka, 1991; 852-853 (Box 11)
      Poet
    - Amiri Baraka, 1976; 1055 (Box 13)
    - Anthony Barboza, October 1983; 854-855 (Box 11)
      Shooting group jazz portrait
    - Anthony Barboza, August 1979; 1169-1170 (Box 15)
      Photographer. In Germany
    - Leticia Barboza, 1980; 856 (Box 11)
      Anthony Barboza's daughter
    - Steven Barboza, 1970s; 857 (Box 11)
      Author. Anthony Barboza's brother
    - Romare Bearden, 1971, 1976; 1056-1060 (Box 13)
    - Romare Bearden, 1976; 1173 (Box 15)
    - Halle Berry, 1998, 2002; 1061-1065 (Box 13)
      Actress. Shot for USA Weekend
    - Halle Berry, 2002; 1171-1172 (Box 15)
    - Halle Berry, 2002; 1924 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Camille Billops, 1978; 858-859 (Box 11)
    - Black Filmmakers, 1994; 860 (Box 11)
      With Matty Rich, Mario Van Peebles, Ernest R. Dickerson, Reginald Hudlin, Warrington Hudlin
      Spike Lee, John Singleton, Charles Love. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - David Bradley, 1979; 1066 (Box 13)
    - David Bradley, 1979; 1235 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Dwight Braxton (Dwight Muhammad Qawi), 1982; 1067-1068 (Box 13)
      Boxer
    - Mark Breland, 1986; 862 (Box 11)
      Boxer. Shot for Essence Magazine
    - Michael J. Britto, 1979; 863 (Box 11)
      Photographer
    - Avery Brooks, December 1984; 864-865 (Box 11)
      Actor
    - Avery Brooks, 1989; 1069-1070a (Box 13)
      Actor. Shot for ABC for "A Man Called Hawk"
    - Avery Brooks, 1984; 1174-1175 (Box 15)
    - Oraston Brooks-El, April 1974; 866 (Box 11)
    - Fred Brown, August 1984; 867 (Box 11)
    - Ed Bullins, 1975; 1071-1074a (Box 13)
      Playwright
    - Hortense Calisher, March 1991; 868-869 (Box 11)
    - Bernard Cameron, 1976; 870-871 (Box 11)
    - Bernard Cameron, 1976; 1075 (Box 13)
      Painter
    - Mrs. Carr, April 1974; 872 (Box 11)
    - Diahann Carroll, 1998; 1076 (Box 13)
      Actress, singer
    - Jeff Chandler, January 1982; 873-875 (Box 11)
      Boxer. For Ring Magazine
    - Cher, 1987; 876-876a (Box 11)
      Actress, Singer. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Cher, 1987; 1077-1077a (Box 13)
      Actress, singer. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Cher, 1987; 1176 (Box 15)
    - Cher, 1987; 1925-1926 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Actress, singer. With Anthony Barboza. Shot for NY Times Sunday Magazine
    - Eddy Chung, 1979; 877 (Box 11)
    - Eddy Chung, 1979; 1078 (Box 13)
    - Dr. John Henrik Clark, August 1974; 883 (Box 11)
      Scholar, historian, professor, author
    - Dr. John Henrik Clarke, August 1974; 1082 (Box 13)
    - Dr. John Henrik Clarke, August 1994; 1177 (Box 15)
    - Dr. John Henrik Clarke, 1974; 1929 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Leroy Clarke, 1974-1977; 878-882 (Box 11)
    - Leroy Clarke, 1974, 1976; 1079-1081 (Box 13)
    - Angelo Colon, 1980; 884-884a (Box 11)
      Designer
    - Angelo Colon, 1980; 1083-1083a (Box 13)
      Fashion designer
    - Larry Colwell, 1968; 1084 (Box 13)
    - Katie Couric, 1999; 885 (Box 11)
      Newscaster
    - Katie Couric, 1997; 1085 (Box 13)
    - Adger Cowans, 1986; 886 (Box 11)
      Artist, photographer
    - Adgar Cowans, 1972; 1086 (Box 13)
    - Adgar Cowans, 1975; 1178 (Box 15)
    - Emilio Cruz, 2003; 1179 (Box 15)
    - Imogen Cunningham, 1972; 887-888b (Box 11)
    - Ossie Davis, 1977; 889-889a (Box 11)
      With Ruby Dee. Actors
    - Ossie Davis, 1977; 1087 (Box 13)
      Actor. With Ruby Dee
    - Ossie Davis, 1977, 1991; 1180-1182 (Box 15)
    - Thulani Davis, 1980; 1006-1008 (Box 12)
      Poet, writer
    - Roy Decarava, 1978; 890 (Box 11)
      Photographer, artist
    - Roy Decarava, 1974; 1183 (Box 15)
      Photographer. With daughter
    - Ruby Dee, 1977; 891 (Box 11)
    - Suzanne De Passe, 1993; 892-894 (Box 11)
      Producer. With mother. Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Laura Dern, 1990; 895 (Box 11)
    - E.L. Doctorow, April 1991; 896 (Box 11)
    - E.L. Doctorow, April 1991; 1088-1089 (Box 13)
    - E.L. Doctorow, April 1991; 1184 (Box 15)
    - Owen Dodson, 1979; 897-899 (Box 11)
    - Owen Dodson, 1979; 1090-1090c (Box 13)
    - Rita Dove, 1993; 900-901 (Box 11)
      Poet. With parents. Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Lou Draper, 1970s; 902 (Box 11)
    - Lou Draper, 1972, 1975; 1091-1092 (Box 13)
    - Bill Duke, 1991; 903 (Box 11)
      Filmmaker
    - James T. Farrell, February 1975; 904 (Box 11)
    - John Farris, 1975; 1093 (Box 13)
    - John Farris, 1975; 1185 (Box 15)
    - Ogundipe Fayomi, 1974; 905 (Box 11)
      Sculptor
    - Ogundipe Fayomi, 1975; 1094-1096 (Box 13)
    - Lafortune Felix, 1990; 906 (Box 11)
      Painter. Shot for Elle Decor Magazine
    - Al Fennar, 1970s; 907 (Box 11)
    - Al Fennar, 1972, 1975; 1097-1098 (Box 13)
      Photographer. With Adgar Cowans, John Pinderhughes
    - James Finney, 1971, 1979; 908-912 (Box 11)
      Hairdresser
    - Ralph Gibson, 1978; 913-914 (Box 11)
    - Ralph Gibson, 1978; 1099 (Box 13)
    - Sam Gilliam, 1988; 915 (Box 11)
    - Sam Gilliam, 1988; 1187-1188 (Box 15)
      Artist. Shot for Life Magazine
    - Sam Gilliam, 1988; 1236 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Allen Ginsberg, January 1987; 1189 (Box 15)
    - Rudy Giuliani, 1987; 1190 (Box 15)
      Politician
    - Archie Givens, Jr., 1998; 1100 (Box 13)
      Director of Givens Foundation for African American Literature, with Emmett Carson. Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Mikhail Gorbachev, 2002; 1927-1928 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Lou Gossett, Jr., 1982; 1191 (Box 15)
      Actor. Shot for Life Magazine
    - Joel Grey, 1987; 916 (Box 11)
    - Joel Grey, 1986; 1101 (Box 13)
    - Joel Grey, 1987; 1192 (Box 15)
    - Bryant Gumbel, 1993; 917-917a (Box 11)
      Journalist
    - Bryant Gumbel, 1993; 1186 (Box 15)
      Journalist. Shot for Bryant Gumbel
    - Marvin Hagler, 1980-1981; 918-920 (Box 11)
      Boxer. Shot for Ring Magazine
    - Marvin Hagler, 1980; 1102-1102a (Box 14)
    - Marvin Hagler, 1980; 1193 (Box 15)
    - Joseph Heller, 1998; 1194 (Box 15)
    - Joseph Heller, 1986; 1237-1237a (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Author. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Linda Hiwot, 1976; 921 (Box 11)
    - Boscoe Holder, 1977; 1195-1196 (Box 15)
    - Geoffrey Holder, 1990; 1197 (Box 15)
      Actor, dancer, artist
    - Geoffrey Holder, 1990; 1930 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Painter, actor, dancer
    - bell hooks, 2000; 922 (Box 11)
    - I'hassah, 1975; 923 (Box 11)
    - I'hassah, 1975; 1104 (Box 14)
    - La Toya Jackson, 1992; 1198 (Box 15)
      Actress, musician
    - Stanley James, 1978; 924 (Box 11)
      Makeup Artist
    - Stanley James, 1978; 1105-1106 (Box 14)
    - Judith Jamison, August 1997; 925 (Box 11)
      Dancer, choreographer
    - Judith Jamison, August 1997; 1199 (Box 15)
    - Betsey Johnson, 1980s; 926 (Box 11)
    - Eddie Bernice Johnson, 1993; 927 (Box 11)
      Congresswoman. Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Magic Johnson, 1987; 1208 (Box 15)
      Basketball player. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Roy Jones, Jr., July 1997; 928 (Box 11)
    - Roy Jones Jr., 1997; 1107-1108 (Box 14)
      Boxer. With friends
    - Kamoinge Workshop, November 1973; 929 (Box 11)
      Albert Fennar, Roy Francis, Herb Randall, Danny Dawson, Beuford Smith, Herb Robinson, Adgar Cowans, Anthony Barboza
      Herman Howard, Ming Smith, Jimmy Mannas, Lou Draper, Calvin Wilson, Shavon Walker
    - Kamoinge Workshop, November 1973; 1200 (Box 15)
    - Stacy Keach, 1970s; 1201 (Box 15)
      Actor. At MOMA for movie premiere
    - Andre Kertesz, 1974; 1931 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Alan Kikuchi-Yngojo, 1980; 930 (Box 11)
    - Jamaica Kincaid, 1990; 1109-1110 (Box 14)
    - Jamaica Kincaid, 1990; 1238-1238a (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Tony King, 1972; 931 (Box 11)
    - Woody King, 1970s; 932 (Box 11)
      Director
    - Maxine Hong Kingston, 1989; 1103-1103a (Box 14)
    - Eartha Kitt, 1992; 1111-1112 (Box 14)
      Actress. Shot for movie "Boomerang"
    - Eartha Kitt, 1992; 1202 (Box 15)
    - Fred Knapp, 2003; 1113 (Box 14)
    - Si Chi Ko, 1978, 1983; 933-936 (Box 11)
      Photographer. With Anthony Barboza
    - Jacob Lawrence, 1972; 937-939 (Box 11)
      Painter. With Gwendolyn Knight
    - Jacob Lawrence, 1972; 1114 (Box 14)
    - Spike Lee, 1239 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Norman Lewis, 1975; 940-940a (Box 11)
    - Norman Lewis, 1976; 1115-1117 (Box 14)
    - Norman Lewis, 1975; 1203-1204 (Box 15)
    - Al Loving, October 1975; 1205-1206 (Box 15)
    - John H. Lucas, Jr., 1993; 941-942 (Box 11)
      Basketball coach. With parents. Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Felipe Luciano, 1978; 943-944 (Box 11)
    - David Lynch, 1989-1990; 945-950 (Box 11)
      At Brooklyn Academy of Music. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - David Lynch, 1990; 1118-1119 (Box 14)
      Filmmaker. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - David Lynch, 1990; 1207-1207b (Box 15)
    - Sylvia Plimack Mangold, 1990; 1126 (Box 14)
      Artist. Shot for Elle Decor Magazine
    - Frank McCourt, 1996; 951-952 (Box 11)
    - Frank McCourt, 1996; 1209-1210 (Box 15)
    - Duane Michals, 1979; 953-953b (Box 11)
    - Bette Midler, 1986; 1120 (Box 14)
      Actress. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Bette Midler, February 1987; 1211-1212 (Box 15)
    - James Mannas, 1975; 1121 (Box 14)
      Film director
    - Barbara Millstein, 1999; 1213-1214 (Box 15)
      Curator of Photos, Brooklyn Museum
    - Walter Mosley, September 1999; 1215-1217 (Box 15)
    - Cecil Murray, 1240 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Reverend
    - Naumiah, 1981; 954 (Box 11)
    - Helen Oji, 1980; 955 (Box 11)
    - Helen Oji, 1980; 1122-1123 (Box 14)
    - Ademola Olugebefola, April 1974; 956-958 (Box 11)
    - Alan C. Page, 1993; 959-960 (Box 11)
      Judge, ex-pro football player. Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Gordon Parks, January 1976; 961 (Box 11)
    - Gordon Parks, 1976; 1124 (Box 14)
    - Deba Patnik, 1996; 1218 (Box 15)
      Rhodes Scholar
    - Shyun-Yien Pei, 1979; 1125 (Box 14)
    - Jim Phillips, 1974; 962-962a (Box 11)
    - Andre Pierre, 1990; 963 (Box 11)
    - P.H. Polk, 1979; 964-965 (Box 11)
    - P.H. Polk, 1974; 1219 (Box 15)
    - Mary Proctor, 1998; 1127 (Box 14)
      Artist. Shot for AARP Magazine
    - Aaron Pryor, 1983; 1128-1130 (Box 14)
    - Dwight Muhammad Qawi, 1982; 861 (Box 11)
    - Quietfire (Ronald Easter), 1979; 966 (Box 11)
    - Quietfire, 1979; 1131 (Box 14)
    - Herb Randall, 1972; 1132-1133 (Box 14)
    - Sam Reed, 1974; 967 (Box 11)
      Graphic Designer
    - Lloyd Richards, 1988; 968 (Box 11)
      Stage Director. Shot for Life Magazine
    - Lloyd Richards, 1998; 1220 (Box 15)
      Director, professor
    - Geraldo Rivera, 1970s; 1221 (Box 15)
      Journalist, attorney, reporter, author, talk show host
    - Howard Rollins, 1981; 1134-1136a (Box 14)
      Actor. Shot for Interview magazine
    - Richard Roundtree, 1971; 969-972 (Box 11)
      Actor, model
    - Richard Roundtree, 1971; 1137 (Box 14)
    - Sonia Sanchez, 1999; 973 (Box 11)
    - Mel Scott, 1980; 974 (Box 11)
      Art director/Picture editor at Life Magazine
    - Oz Scott, 1978; 975-977 (Box 11)
      Stage director
    - Ntozake Shange, 1977; 1138 (Box 14)
      Poet, playwright
    - Ntozake Shange, 1977; 1222 (Box 15)
    - John Singleton, 1991; 978 (Box 11)
      Film director. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - John Singleton, 1994; 1139-1140a (Box 14)
    - John Singleton, October 1994; 1223 (Box 15)
    - Sister Souljah, 1994; 1141-1144 (Box 14)
      Author, activist
    - Beuford Smith, 1974; 979-980 (Box 11)
    - Beuford Smith, 1972; 1145 (Box 14)
    - Charles Smith, April 1974; 981 (Box 11)
    - Jamyl Smith, 1970s; 982 (Box 11)
    - Luong Smith, 1970s; 996 (Box 11)
    - Ming Smith, 1970s; 983 (Box 11)
    - Morgan Smith and Marvin Smith, 1982; 984 (Box 11)
      Photographers
    - Morgan and Marvin Smith, 1982; 1146 (Box 14)
    - Vincent Smith, 1975-1976; 985-995 (Box 11)
    - Vincent Smith, 1975; 1224-1227 (Box 15)
    - Wole Soyinka, September 1996; 997-1000 (Box 11)
      Writer. Shot for New Yorker Magazine
    - Wole Soyinka, 1996; 1147-1148 (Box 14)
    - Wole Soyinka, 1996; 1228-1230 (Box 15)
      Author. Shot for New Yorker Magazine
    - Evelyn Thomas, 1975; 1149 (Box 14)
    - Evelyn Thomas, 1975; 1231 (Box 15)
    - U.S. (Kid) Thompson, March 1974; 1001-1005 (Box 12)
      Dancer, manager, husband of Florence Mills. With Dr. Helen Johnson
    - U.S. (Kid) Thompson, 1974; 1150 (Box 14)
      Dancer, manager, husband of Florence Mills
    - Denessa Tobin, 1980; 1009 (Box 12)
    - Quincy Troupe, 1980; 1010 (Box 12)
    - Quincy Troupe, 1980; 1151-1151a (Box 14)
    - Eric Turner, 1979; 1011-1012 (Box 12)
      Hairdresser. With Jessica Hagedorn, poet
    - Valery, 1977; 1013 (Box 12)
    - James Vanderzee, 1971-1980; 1014-1030 (Box 12)
      Photographer. Shooting Bill Cosby. With Anthony Barboza, Roy Decarava, Donna Vanderzee
    - James Vanderzee, 1980; 1152-1153 (Box 14)
    - James Vanderzee, 1981; 1241 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Derek Walcott, 1978; 1154 (Box 14)
    - Derek Walcott, 1978; 1232 (Box 15)
    - Alice Walker, 1989; 1155-1156 (Box 14)
      Writer. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Alice Walker, 1989; 1233-1234 (Box 15)
    - Shawn Walker, 1978; 1034 (Box 12)
    - Shawn Walker, 1972; 1157 (Box 14)
    - Michelle Wallace, 1978; 1031-1033 (Box 12)
      Author. With mother (Faith Ringgold) grandmother, great grandmother
    - Michelle Wallace, 1978; 1158-1158b (Box 14)
    - Damon Wayans, 1987; 1035 (Box 12)
      Actor, comedian
    - Peter Westbrook, 1997; 1159-1160 (Box 14)
      Fencer. Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Dr. James H. Williams, July 1993; 1036-1037 (Box 12)
      Professor
    - John A. Williams, 1979; 1161 (Box 14)
    - Vanessa Williams, October 1984; 1038 (Box 12)
    - Lee Witkin, 1978; 1039-1041 (Box 12)
      Photo Curator
    - Lee Witkin, 1978; 1162-1163 (Box 14)
      Photo curator
    - Lee Witkin, 1978; 1932-1937 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Photographer, and his gallery
    - James Woody, 1979; 1042-1042a (Box 12)
    - Michael Wright, 1983-1984; 1043-1045 (Box 12)
  - Fashion
    - A and S (Abraham and Strauss) Department Store Series, 1977; 1276-1340 (Box 17)
    - A and S Department Store, 1970s; 1465 (Box 19)
    - Avon Advertisement, 1980s; 1341-1342a (Box 17)
    - Barbados Fashion Shoot, May 1999; 1436-1439 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Beauty Test, 1990s; 1343 (Box 17)
    - Dance Shoot, 1970s; 1242 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ebony Men's Magazine, 1980s; 1440-1447 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Essence Fashion Shoot, 1970s; 1344 (Box 17)
    - Essence Fashion Shoot, 1970s; 1448-1448a (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Essence Magazine, 1970s; 1466 (Box 19)
    - Pat Evans, 1969-1970; 1467-1470 (Box 19)
      Fashion Shoots
    - Fashion Shoots, 1969-1970s, 1999; 1471-1484 (Box 19)
    - Fashion Tests, 1970s-2003; 1345-1351 (Box 17)
    - Terry Freeman (sic), 1980s; 1485-1486 (Box 19)
    - Glenda, 1981; 1487 (Box 19)
      Model
    - GQ Dancers, 1970s; 1352-1354 (Box 17)
    - Gym Boys, 2000s; 1449 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Harper's Bazaar, 1969; 1449a (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Harper's Bazaar, 1969; 1488-1488e (Box 19)
    - Iman, 1970s-1979; 1355-1358 (Box 17)
      Model Tests
    - Iman, 1975-1979; 1489-1492 (Box 19)
    - Grace Jones, 1970s; 1359-1360 (Box 18)
    - Joy, 1980s; 1361-1363 (Box 18)
    - Joy, 1980; 1493 (Box 19)
    - Lingerie Test, 1990s; 1364 (Box 18)
    - Lucy, July 1980; 1450 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Model Test
    - Mayisha, 1975, 1980; 1365-1366 (Box 18)
    - Ming, 1970s; 1367-1379 (Box 18)
    - Models, 1970s; 1451 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Model Test, 1970s; 1243 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Model Tests, 1970s-2000s; 1380-1422 (Box 18)
    - Model Tests, 1990s-2000s; 1452-1464 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Model Tests, 1970s-1990s; 1494-1503 (Box 19)
    - Model Tests, 1970s, 2000s; 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Margaret Rome [sic], 1976; 1423-1427 (Box 18)
    - Shanachie Records Shoot, 1999-2000; 1504-1505 (Box 19)
    - Ming Smith, 1970s; 1506-1512 (Box 19)
    - Toukie Smith, 1980; 1428-1430 (Box 18)
      Model. With Willie Smith
    - Toukie Smith, 1978-1980s; 1513-1516 (Box 19)
    - Studio Portrait, 1990s; 1431 (Box 18)
    - Terry, 1980s; 1432 (Box 18)
    - Gary Thomas, 1979; 1433 (Box 18)
    - Gary Thomas and Quietfire, 1980s; 1517 (Box 19)
    - Toko Zellie, 1976; 1434-1435 (Box 18)
    - Toko Zellie, 1971; 1518 (Box 19)
  - People and Places
    - Bali, Indonesia, 1993; 1244 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bali, Indonesia, 1993; 1519 (Box 20)
    - Bali, Indonesia, 1992-1993; 1689-1695 (Box 22)
    - Bali, Indonesia, 1987; 1766-1766a (Box 23)
    - Brazil, 1984; 1245 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Brazil, 1984; 1792 (Box 24)
    - Brooklyn Gang, 1995; 1520 (Box 20)
    - Cape Cod, Massachusetts, 1970s; 1521-1522 (Box 20)
    - Cape Cod, Massachusetts, 1970s; 1696 (Box 22)
    - Cairo, Egypt, 1972; 1523 (Box 20)
    - Cairo, Egypt, 1973; 1793-1800 (Box 24)
    - Casablanca, Morocco, 1978; 1697 (Box 22)
    - Cayar, Senegal, 1973; 1524 (Box 20)
    - Charlotte, North Carolina, 1987; 1525 (Box 20)
      Fashion Shoot
    - Coney Island, New York, 1970s; 1526-1535 (Box 20)
    - Coney Island, New York, 1970s; 1698-1705 (Box 22)
    - Coney Island, New York, 1970s; 1767 (Box 23)
    - Asiba Danso, 1976; 1536 (Box 20)
      Great Neck, New York
    - Ethiopia, 1973; 1537 (Box 20)
    - Ethiopia, 1973; 1706 (Box 22)
    - Ethiopia, 1973; 1801-1803 (Box 24)
    - Florida, 1966; 1769-1769a (Box 23)
    - Halloween Parade, 1980s; 1538-1541 (Box 20)
      New York City
    - Harlem, New York, 1970s; 1542-1545 (Box 20)
    - Harlem, New York, 1970s, 2002; 1707-1708 (Box 22)
    - Harlem Dance Theater, 1983; 1546-1547 (Box 20)
      Shot for GEO Magazine
    - Dance Theater of Harlem, New York City, 1983; 1768 (Box 23)
      Shot for Geo Magazine
    - Hoboken, New Jersey, 1970s; 1709-1713 (Box 22)
    - Israel, 1994; 1941-1946 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Israel, 1994; 1714-1715 (Box 22)
      Dimona. Shot for "Day in the Life of Israel"
    - Israel - Jerusalem, 1994; 1805-1807 (Box 24)
    - Jacksonville, Florida, 1968; 1940 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Jacksonville, Florida, 1967-1968; 1548-1563 (Box 20)
    - Jacksonville, Florida, 1967-1968; 1716-1722 (Box 22)
    - Jacksonville, Florida, 1968; 1770-1780 (Box 23)
    - Jamaica, 1996; 1804 (Box 24)
    - Long Island, New York, 2004; 1808 (Box 24)
      Tri-County Flea Market
    - The Louvre Museum. Paris, France, 1985; 1564 (Box 20)
      Mona Lisa
    - Los Angeles, California, 1980; 1248-1248a (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Mexico, 1972; 1781 (Box 23)
    - Mexico - Ensenada, 1980; 1949 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 1)
    - Morocco, 1978; 1723-1728 (Box 22)
      Fes, Casablanca, Goulmima
    - Morocco, 1978; 1782-1783 (Box 23)
      Fes, Fatima
    - Morocco, 1978; 1809-1812a (Box 24)
      Casablanca, Fatima
    - New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1970s; 1729 (Box 22)
    - New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1972; 1784 (Box 23)
    - New York City, 1960s-1980s; 1565-1663 (Box 21)
      People on the streets, Vietnam Protest, Puerto Rican parade, Halloween parade
    - New York City, 1969-1970s; 1730-1752 (Box 22)
      People on the street, Halloween Parade
    - New York City, 1970s; 1785-1787 (Box 23)
      Halloween
    - New York City, 1970s-1980s; 1813-1814 (Box 24)
    - Palatka, Florida, 1968; 1664-1669 (Box 21)
    - Palatka, Florida, 1968; 1753-1756 (Box 22)
    - Palatka, Florida, 1968; 1815 (Box 24)
    - Pensacola, Florida, 1966; 1670-1680 (Box 21)
      Ringling Bros
    - Pensacola, Florida, 1966; 1757-1759 (Box 22)
    - Pensacola, Florida, 1966; 1816 (Box 24)
      Clyde Beatty Circus
    - Providence, Rhode Island, 1970s; 1681-1683 (Box 21)
      Knocka, 96 years old
    - Senegal - Gore Island, 1973; 1247 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Senegal, 1978; 1684 (Box 21)
      Dakar
    - Senegal, 1972-1978; 1760-1762 (Box 22)
      Dakar, Fadiouth
    - Senegal, 1978; 1788-1790 (Box 23)
    - Senegal, 1973, 1980; 1817-1821 (Box 24)
      Dakar, Cayor, Goree Island
    - Trinidad, West Indies - Carnival, 1977; 1246-1246a (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Trinidad, 1977; 1685 (Box 21)
    - Trinidad, 1977; 1822-1823 (Box 24)
    - Warrington, Florida, 1966; 1686-1687 (Box 21)
    - Warrington, Florida, 1966; 1763-1765 (Box 22)
    - Washington D.C., 2001; 1791 (Box 23)
      School kids for Microsoft Advertisement
    - Watts, Los Angeles, 1980; 1688 (Box 21)
      Vietnam Vet, shot for Life Magazine
  - Miscellaneous
    - Advertisements, 1990s; 1824-1826 (Box 25)
    - Alexio and Lien Barboza (daughters), 2000s; 1831 (Box 25)
      On Jones Beach, NY
    - Anthony Barboza Promotional Materials, 1249-1250a (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Anthony Barboza Promotional Materials, 1827-1830a (Box 25)
    - Anthony Barboza, 1967; 1871 (Box 26)
      In US Navy, in Jacksonville, Florida
    - Anthony Barboza Self Portraits, 1975-1991; 1866-1870 (Box 26)
    - Anthony Barboza, 1984; 1872-1873 (Box 26)
      With members of Japanese film crew. Shooting Miles Davis TV commercial
    - Anthony Barboz Self-Portrait, 1979-1982; 1268-1275 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Anthony Barboza Promotional Photographs, 1874-1885 (Box 26)
    - Craig Barboza, 1990s; 1886-1886a (Box 26)
      Anthony Barboza's brother
    - Baseball Test Shot, 2000s; 1887 (Box 26)
    - Black Dreams / White Sheets Series, 1996-2000; 1252-1262 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      "Bonded"; "Eyewitness to the Prosecution"; "Klu Klux Klan"; "Margarita"; "Nigger"; "Ju Ju MAN"
      "Tupac and Biggie"; "Malcolm X"; "Music Mind"; untitled; "Jackie Robinson"
    - Black Dreams / White Sheets, 1996-1999; 1832-1850 (Box 25)
      "Black Power," "Drag Queen," "Lynched," "Chained and Gagged," "Not Matter," "Passing on the Knowledge,"
      "AIDS," "He Said! She Said!," "Black and White," "Black and White," "Blackface," "Dead Presidents,"
      "Tribal," "Pharaoh," "Gassed," "Rape," "Mother Africa,"
    - Black Dreams / White Sheets, 1996-2002; 1888-1910 (Box 26)
      "Africa," "Bonded," "Blackface," "Communicate," Drag Queen," "Father and Sons," "Head-Music"
      "He Said! She Said!," "I Mean Business," "Islam," "Ju Ju MAN," "Malcolm X," "Morgue"
      "Mother Future," "Muhammed Ali," "Passage," "Slave Doll," "Tupac and Biggie"
    - Book Cover, 1251 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Steven Barboza - American Jihad
    - Book Cover - Randall Cunningham's "I'm Still Scrambling", 1263 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Coors Brewing Company Black History Ads, 1993; 1911-1912 (Box 26)
    - The Dolan Sisters "Satellite Sisters' Uncommon Senses" Book Jacket, 2001; 1913 (Box 26)
    - Ear Magazine of New Music, 1986; 1859 (Box 25)
      Features Anthony Barboza Photography
    - Equal Justice Calendar, 2001; 1851 (Box 25)
      Photos by Anthony Barboza
    - General Motors Ads, 1998; 1914-1915 (Box 26)
    - Ghost Series, 1976; 1264 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Greyhound Ad, 1987; 1916 (Box 26)
      Ebony Fashion Fair
    - Harper's Bazaar Advertisement, 1970s; 1854-1856 (Box 25)
    - In The Arts Portfolio, 1983; 1857 (Box 25)
    - Los Angeles, California, 1980; 1265-1266 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Man. Shot for Life Magazine
    - Newsweek "What Color Is Black?" Cover, 1995; 1917 (Box 26)
    - Nissan Advertisements, 1860-1861 (Box 25)
      Featuring Anthony Barboza and his photography
    - Paper Dance, 1976; 1852-1853 (Box 25)
      Ghost Series
    - "Progressions" - Calendar, 1970; 1267 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Reebok Advertisement, 1990s; 1862 (Box 25)
    - Seagrams Advertisement, 1863 (Box 25)
      Featuring Aaron Pryor
    - Shanachie Records Album Cover, 2000s; 1864 (Box 25)
    - "Still I See Ya. The Voices", 1993; 1858 (Box 25)
    - Studio Crew, 1978; 1865 (Box 25)
    - Untitled Series, 1998; 1918-1920 (Box 26)
- Posters